

Summary

As an experienced developer who is a core part of my project teams, I deliver high quality codes which meet or exceed the requirements. I help you solve problems with front end, back end, and mobile app development, performance boosting, defect fixing, and even more. My soft skills also guarantee me to output the maximum productivity as well as to support teammates when they need help.

Employment

Accenture Toronto Software Developer Spring | ASP.NET Core | Angular

June 2021 to Current

- Implement and deliver story features of mobile application in an agile sprint framework, with the unit test coverage reaching 90%.
- Improve the performance of a sub-system by 75% in its loading time via code refactoring and optimization.
- Maintain production apps, fix defects, and expand existing features.

Revature Toronto

Full Stack Developer Spring | Angular

Mar. 2021 to July 2022

- Implement story features on banking project and reimbursement system, with 15% of functionalities exceeding the user expectation.
- Contribute backend codes to bug bounty board application, support on debugging, and unit testing.

Somoplay North York Software developer May 2020 to Dec. 2020

- Develop website landing page, admin management portal, and email template system.
- Trouble-shoot issues on data rendering, website optimization, and fix defects.

Torneo Toronto

Company Collaborator

Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2020

- Implement stand-alone blog module components, and its content editing system.
- Develop website responsive sign-in/register page, and mobile navigation component.

Projects

Bug Bounty V1 Mar. 2021 to June 2021

Bug Bounty is an application designed for business and development level users to report and track bugs on the internal applications used in Revature.

Simple Trader Mar. 2021 to June 2021

Simple Trader is an online marketplace platform that provides a convenient way for people to buy and sell things.

Expense Reimbursement System

Mar. 2021 to Apr. 2021

Expense Reimbursement System manages the process of reimbursing employees for expenses incurred during company time.

Avoid The Bricks Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2019

HTML5 game developed with jQuery where player avoids the falling bricks and survive as long as possible.

Certifications

Contact

guannanlv@gmail.com

https://glv1at118.github.io/guannanportfolio-terminal/

905-519-2561

Education

University of Toronto

Sept. 2016 to June

Master's Degree Engineering 2018

Skills

BACK END & DATABASE

Java FE

Spring Framework

Hibernate

C#

.NET Core

Entity Framework Core

Node.js

Express

PostgreSQL

Microsoft SQL Server

MongoDB

Kinvey

RabbitMQ

Firebase

MyBatis

FRONT END & MOBILE

Javascript

Typescript

React

Angular

Vue

iQuery

lonic Framework

PrimeNG

Bootstrap

NativeScript

DEVOPS & MISC

AWS

Azure

Git

Docker

Linux

Jenkins